Capital District Regional Planning Commission; Records apap380
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Albany County, 1942-2013; 1; 11.42 cubic ft.
  - Albany County, Drive It Yourself Tour of Albany County, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Albany County, Economic Profile, 1977 June-1977 September (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Albany County, Environmental Clearance Worksheet, 1972 November (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Albany County, Environmental/Section 4(f) Statement Administrative Action for Interstate Route 687, Route 85, Albany-Schenectady Route, Undated (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Albany County, Evaluation of Recreational Program Participation and Distribution of Properties and Facilities by Census Tract, 1976 August (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Albany County, Feasibility Study for the Patroon Creek Daylighting Project at Tivoli Nature Preserve, 2013 March (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Albany County, Feasibility Study of the Intergovernmental Cooperation in the Hill Towns of Albany County, Undated (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Albany County, Final Design Report P.I.N.1051 .43 South Mall Expressway to South 378 Interchange, 1991 February (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Albany County, Final Environmental Impact Statement for the Extension of Runway 1-19…, 1979 May (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Albany County, Financial Report Recreational Plan Committee, 1976 May (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Albany County, Geology and Land Uses in the Pine Bush Albany County, New York, Circular 47, 1975 October (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Albany County, The Geology of the Pine Bush and Its Environmental Implications, 1973 September (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Albany County, Group Interviews with Senior Citizens Clubs, Technical Report, 1976 November-1976 December (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Albany County, Helderberg Escarpment Planning Guide, 2002 February (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Albany County, Heilman Property: A Master Plan for Land Use, 1975 April (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Albany County, Historic Cohoes, New York: A Survey of Historic Resources, 1971 June (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Albany County, Homeless Older Adolescent (16-21) Needs in Albany County, 1984 November (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Albany County, Housing Assistance: A Compendium of Programs and Available Resources for Housing Providers and Consumers in Albany County, 1979 May (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Albany County, Housing Resources Analysis Albany County, New York, 1972 October (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Albany County, Identification of Intergovernmental Planning Linkages, 1979 June (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Albany County, Inventory of Church Facilities, Technical Report, 1976 June (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Albany County, Inventory of Recreational Facilities Technical Report, 1976 May (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Albany County, Landslide and Erosion Susceptibility within the Norman's Kill Drainage Basin, 1979 June (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Albany County, Long Range Plan 1985-1990, Senior Service Centers of Albany Area, Inc., 1985 September (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Albany County, Market Analysis and Public Assembly Facility Enhancement Strategy, 1997 July (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Albany County, Memorandum EC1, Heat Transfer Principles [Informational Brochure], 1978 May (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Albany County, National Areas of Albany County, 2nd Edition [Guidebook], Undated (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Albany County, Memorandum EC4, Solar Energy Theories Sensitized for Applications in Albany County, New York, 1979 May (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Albany County, Needs Assessment of the Emergency Shelter Delivery System in Albany County, 1981 June (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Albany County, News Clippings, Undated (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Albany County, Operation Pinebush, 1971 December (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Albany County, Operation Pinebush, The Nature Conservancy, Eastern New York Chapter, Undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Albany County, Overall Economic Development Plan, Albany County, 1977 March (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Albany County, Phase 2 Design Report, Albany Crosstown Extension (I-90-I-687) Northside Northway Extension (I-87 -Route 85) Albany Crosstown (I-87), 1972 May (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Albany County, Phase 2 Solid Waste Resource Recovery Feasibility Analysis (1 of 2), 1985 April (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Albany County, Phase 2 Solid Waste Resource Recovery Feasibility Analysis (2 of 2), 1985 April (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Albany County, Phase 2 Solid Waste Resource Recovery Feasibility Analysis, Executive Summary, 1985 April (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Albany County, Pine Bush: Albany's Last Frontier, 1976 April (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Albany County, Pine Bush Alternate Master Plan, Discussion Draft, 1975 May (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Albany County, The Pine Bush Intermunicipal Study, 1979 March (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Albany County, The Pine Bush Intermunicipal Study, Technical Report, 1980 January (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Albany County, Pine Bush Report [Maps and Figures], 1973 October (Flat-file 1)
  - Albany County, The Pine Bush: A Special Study of Natural Resource of A Unique Area, RPI School of Architecture, 1974 March (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Albany County, Pine Bush Study, Natural-Physical Section, Undated (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Albany County, Pine Bush Unique Area Unit Management Plan, 1986 January (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Albany County, The Potential for Outdoor Recreation Activity in Albany County [Report], Undated (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Albany County, A Poverty Profile of Albany and Albany County, New York, 1973 June (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Albany County, Preliminary Report on the Limestones of Albany County, New York, 1958 May (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Albany County, Profile of Albany County, New York, Undated (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Albany County, Project Report I-IV, Krumkill Road Route 85 to New Scotland Avenue, 1975 August (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Albany County, The Public Financing of Recreational and Leisure Time Activities in Albany County, 1976 April (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Albany County, Recreation and Leisure Time Services Plan for Albany County, 1976 December (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Albany County, Recreation and Open Space Plan, 1972 December (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Albany County, Recreation Plan Study, Special Report, 1976 October (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Albany County, A Recreational Plan for Albany County, Council of Community Services, 1976 December (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Albany County, Regulation of Mobile/Manufactured Home Siting in Albany County, 1983 January (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Albany County, Report to the County Executive on the Need for a Comprehensive Geographic Information System for Albany County New York, 1977 April (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Albany County, A Review of Municipal and Neighborhood Land Uses, 1975 May (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Albany County, The Senior Citizen in Albany County, Recreation Plan Committee, 1976 August (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Albany County, SEQR Notice of Determination of Non-Significance [Re: 2-Lane Extension of Erie Blvd. In Menands], Undated (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Albany County, Soil Interpretation Report, 1974 January (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Albany County, Soil Interpretation Report Pine Bush and Surrounding Area, 1974 January (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Albany County, Soil Survey of Pine Bush and Surrounding Area [Map], Undated (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Albany County, Technical Memorandum EC2: Climate, Wind and Heat Loss, 1978 May (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Albany County, Technical Memorandum EC-3: Conductance, Resistance and Recommended Standards, 1978 May (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Albany County, Technical Memorandum LUI-06: Energy Features and Facilities, 1977 May (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Albany County, Technical Report on Selected Facilities Albany County, New York, 1975-1976, 1976 October (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Albany County, The Teens In Albany County 1975 [Special Report], 1976 October (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Albany County, This Is Albany County, Directory from League of Women Voters of Albany County, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Albany County, Unit Management Plan, Pine Bush Unique Area, 1985 June (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Albany County, Watervliet-Guilderland Investigation of Consolidation of Water Supply and Filtration Services, 2012 March (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Albany County, What The Readership Thinks: A Survey of the Leisure-Time Activities and Interests of 836 Respondents to a Newspaper Survey, 1976 January (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - [Village of] Altamont, Altamont Annexation Summary Report, 1984 September (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - [Village of] Altamont, Annual Budget, 1967-1968 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - [Village of] Altamont, Draft Development Plan, 1968 December (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - [Village of] Altamont, Re: Altamont Railway Depot Building [Correspondence and Newspaper Articles], 1968 November (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - [Village of] Altamont, Report on Water Supply Distribution, 1967 March (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - [Town of] Berne, Land Use Survey Data [Berne Master Plan Committee], 1989 October (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - [Town of] Bethlehem, Community Characteristics Population Trend Land Use, 1964 November (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - [Town of] Bethlehem, Development Plan for the Route 9W Corridor, 1989 March (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - [Town of] Bethlehem, Draft Generic Environmental Impact statement, Master Plan, 1994 October (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - [Town of] Bethlehem, Master Plan, 1965 December (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - [Town of] Bethlehem, Natural Resource and Open Space Inventory, Interim Wetlands Report, 1974 July (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - [Town of] Bethlehem, Ordinance… for Regulating the Operation of House-Trailers and House-Trailer Camps Within the Town…, 1962 January (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - [Town of] Bethlehem, A Preliminary Analysis of Law Flows at Selected Sites in the Southern Part of the Town…, 1968 November (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - [Town of] Bethlehem, Proposed Extension No 8 to the Delmar-Elsmere Sewer District, 1969 August (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - [Town of] Bethlehem, Proposed N.Y. Central Railroad Extension [Application to Water Resources Commission], 1967 April (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - [Town of] Bethlehem, Public Participation Report No. 2, Town Planning Survey: Bethlehem's Future Directions, 1991 August (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - [Town of] Bethlehem, Report on Wastewater Facility Plan (1 of 2), 1979 May (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - [Town of] Bethlehem, Report on Wastewater Facility Plan (2 of 2), 1979 May (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - [Town of] Bethlehem, Requirements for Approval of Subdivisions…, 1968 January (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - [Town of] Bethlehem, A Study of the Effect of Declining Enrollment on the Bethlehem Central School District's Elementary School Housing Needs, 1975 December (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - [Town of] Bethlehem, Subdivision Regulation, Chapter 103, 1997 August (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - [Town of] Bethlehem, This is the Town of Bethlehem [Booklet from League of Women Voters], 1973 October (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - [Town of] Bethlehem, To the Citizens of Bethlehem, [FAQ from Owens/Corning President], Undated (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - [Town of] Bethlehem, Town of Bethlehem: A Brief History, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - [Town of] Bethlehem, Traffic Study of the Potential Delmar Bypass Extension and Improvement/Extension of Fisher Boulevard, 1985 April (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - [Town of] Bethlehem, Zoning-Chapter 128, 1997 August (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - [Town of] Coeymans and Village of Ravena, Comprehensive Plan (1 of 2), 1970 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - [Town of] Coeymans and Village of Ravena, Comprehensive Plan (2 of 2), 1970 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - [Town of] Coeymans, Comprehensive Plan, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - [Town of] Coeymans, Open Space Study [Technical Notes], 1974 September (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - [Town of] Coeymans and Westerlo, Transportation Project Report, Route 32 (1 of 3), 1987 December (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - [Town of] Coeymans and Westerlo, Transportation Project Report, Route 32 (2 of 3), 1987 December (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - [Town of] Coeymans and Westerlo, Transportation Project Report, Route 32 (3 of 3), 1987 December (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - [Town of] Cohoes, Application for Workable Program Certification or Re-Certification, 1971 July (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - [Town of] Cohoes, Central Area Plan and Technical Studies, 1973 October (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - [Town of] Cohoes, Central Business District [Confidential Unofficial Draft], Undated (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - [Town of] Cohoes, Cohoes Central Area: Transportation, 1973 June (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - [Town of] Cohoes, Cohoes: A Study of the Regional Housing Market, 1971 April (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - [Town of] Cohoes, Comprehensive Plan, 1967 June (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - [Town of] Cohoes, Dimensions in Progress: A Model Cities Program [Booklet], 1972 April (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - [Town of] Cohoes, Economic and Market Analysis Study, Neighborhood Development Program, 1973 January (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - [Town of] Cohoes, Economic and Marketing Survey, 1974 March (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - [Town of] Cohoes, The Erie Canal Recreation Way, 1972 January (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - [Town of] Cohoes, Federal Aid Application, Proposed Plan for Additional $250,000 Allocation, 1974 March (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - [Town of] Cohoes, Final Draft Cohoes 2000, 1992 January (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - [Town of] Cohoes, Final Model Cities Program [Federal Aid Application], 1974 June (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - [Town of] Cohoes, Final Model Cities Program, [Federal Aid Application], 1975 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - [Town of] Cohoes, Housing: A Framework for Action, 1971 June (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - [Town of] Cohoes, A Look at Cohoes In the Mid-70's, 1974 August (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - [Town of] Cohoes, Master Plan, 1992 March (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - [Town of] Cohoes, Neighborhood Development Program for Action Year 1972-1973, 1972 May (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - [Town of] Cohoes, Recreation Master Plan, 1973 June (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - [Town of] Cohoes, Residential Printouts From Modeling Effort…, 1973 May (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - [Town of] Cohoes, Softex Manufacturing Expansion, 2002 January (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - [Town of] Cohoes, Water Distribution System Network Analysis, 1982 February (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - [Town of] Cohoes, Zoning Ordinance, 1992 June (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - [Town of] Colonie, 1980 Census of Population, Characteristics of People and Housing, Undated (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - [Town of] Colonie, Colonie Senior Housing Section 202 Application (1 of 2), 1991 September (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - [Town of] Colonie, Colonie Senior Housing Section 202 Application (2 of 2), 1991 September (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - [Town of] Colonie, Community Development 1995 Consolidated Plan, 1994 October (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - [Town of] Colonie, Comprehensive Land Use Study, 1972 August (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - [Town of] Colonie, Crescent Area 201 Facilities Plan C-36-1209, 1983 September (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - [Town of] Colonie, Draft Generic Environmental Impact Statement, Lisha Kill-Kings Road Area (1 of 2), 1996 March (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - [Town of] Colonie, Draft Generic Environmental Impact Statement, Lisha Kill-Kings Road Area (2 of 2), 1996 March (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - [Town of] Colonie, Environmental Assessment, Removal of Obstructions to Runway End 01, 1987 August (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - [Town of] Colonie, Environmental Assessment, Removal of Obstructions to Runway End 19, 1986 July (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - [Town of] Colonie, Environmental Impact Assessment Report, Passenger Terminal Building and Apron Extension, 1978 August (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - [Town of] Colonie, Environmental Assessment Survey for the Proposed Mohawk View Water Pollution Control Plant…, 1974 January (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - [Town of] Colonie, Final Generic Environmental Impact Statement, Lisha Kill-Kings Road Area, (1 of 2), 1996 May (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - [Town of] Colonie, Final Generic Environmental Impact Statement, Lisha Kill-Kings Road Area, (2 of 2), 1996 May (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - [Town of] Colonie, A Guide to the Colonie Bike Path, Undated (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - [Town of] Colonie, Joint Statement of Findings, Final Generic Environmental Impact Statement Airport Area, 1992 January (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - [Town of] Colonie, Land Management Study Watervliet-Shaker Historic and Recreational District, 1973 September (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - [Town of] Colonie, Land Use Management Technical Report, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - [Town of] Colonie, Lisha Kill-Kings Road Area Generic Environmental Impact Statement Joint Statement of Findings, 1996 June (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - [Town of] Colonie, Master Plan, 1959 July (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - [Town of] Colonie, Master Plan (1 of 2), 2003 March (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - [Town of] Colonie, Master Plan (2 of 2), 2003 March (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - [Town of] Colonie, Northford Corporation Sanitary Landfill-Kings Road [Engineering Report], 1968 September (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - [Town of] Colonie, A Place Called Colonie… [Promotional Brochure], 1989 January (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - [Town of] Colonie, Preservation Country-Style: Land Management Comes First The Case of the Watervliet-Shaker Historic District, 1974 July (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - [Town of] Colonie, Pure Waters Program, 1969 January (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - [Town of] Colonie, Pure Waters Program, Map, 1968 December (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - [Town of] Colonie, Report on Comprehensive Sewerage Study, 1965 June (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - [Town of] Colonie, The Street or Highway Resolution of the Town of Colonie, 1972 December (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - [Town of] Colonie, Street Trees for Colonie, A Guideline for the Town, 1986 August (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - [Town of] Colonie, Subdivision of Land, Chapter 166, Undated (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - [Village of] Green Island, Analysis of Workload Green Island Police Department, 1982 May (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - [Village of] Green Island, Green Island Expansion Hydroelectric Project, 1986 February (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - [Village of] Green Island, Green Island Yesterday and Today, [Periodicals], Undated (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - [Village of] Green Island, Local Law #3, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - [Village of] Green Island, Waterfront Revitalization Program [Draft Report], 1986 March (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - [Town of] Guilderland, Development Plan Town of Guilderland and Village of Altamont, New York (1 of 2), 1969 October (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - [Town of] Guilderland, Development Plan Town of Guilderland and Village of Altamont, New York (2 of 2), 1969 October (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - [Town of] Guilderland, Draft Development Plan, 1969 March (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - [Town of] Guilderland, Draft Generic Environmental Impact Study, [Request for Rezoning], 1981 May (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - [Town of] Guilderland, Final Generic Environmental Impact Study, [Request for Rezoning], 1981 June (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - [Town of] Guilderland, Transportation Project Report, Phase 2, Guilderland Center, Route 146 Over Penn Central Railroad, 1978 November (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - [Town of] Guilderland, Wastewater Facilities Report, Krumkill Drainage Basin Improvement Area, 1969 February (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - [Town of] Guilderland, Your Industrial Site in Guilderland N.Y. [Promotional Booklet], 1977 September (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - [Town of] Guilderland, Zoning Law of the Town of Guilderland, 1992 March (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - [Town of] Knox, Land Use Guide and Map, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - [Hamlet of] Loudonville, Weare C. Little Memorial Park, Undated (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - [Village of] Menands, Report on Comprehensive Sewerage Study Albany Metropolitan Area, 1965 June (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - [Town of] New Scotland, Preliminary Plans and Report on Water Resource Study, 1964 March (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - [Village of] Ravena, Report on Water System, 1966 March (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - [Village of] Ravena, Summary: Village Plan, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - [Town of] Rensselaerville, The Conference Center of the Institute on Man and Science [Promotional Booklet], Undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - [Town of] Rensselaerville, SEQR/SERP Determination Resolution, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - [Village of] Voorheesville, Responsiveness Summaries for the Village of Voorheesville Public Informational Meetings, 1982 April (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - [Village of] Voorheesville, Responsiveness Summary of the Public Hearing for the Village of Voorheesville Wastewater Facility Plan, 1983 February (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - [Village of] Voorheesville, Responsiveness Summary of the Public Informational Meeting for the Village of Voorheesville Wastewater Facility Plan, 1982 December (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - [Village of] Voorheesville, Wastewater Facilities Plan [Public Hearing Notice], 1983 February (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - [City of] Watervliet, General Plan, 1961 July (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - [City of] Watervliet, Hudson Shores [Promotional Booklet], 1969 December (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - [City of] Watervliet, Summary of Application for Non-Capacity Related Amendment, Normanskill Hydroelectric Facility, 2005 July (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - [City of] Watervliet, Van Rensselaer Village, 1972 August (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - [City of] Watervliet, Van Rensselaer Village, [Promotional Booklet], Undated (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - [City of] Watervliet, Water Distribution System Network Analysis, 1981 October (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - [City of] Watervliet, Waterfront Revitalization Program [Interim Report], 1985 August (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - [City of] Watervliet, Waterfront Revitalization Program [Draft Report], 1986 March (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - [Town of] Westerlo, National Resource and Open Space Inventory, Wetlands Survey, 1974 August (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Saratoga County, 1960-2008; 2; 9.68 cubic ft.
  This series contains files pertaining to planning decisions in Saratoga County, New York. Some of the documents refer to plans for specific municipalities -- i.e., villages, towns, and the City of Saratoga Springs -- while others pertain to county-wide planning efforts. Among the most common file types are: comprehensive/master plans (including master plans for Saratoga Springs published in the 1960s and 1980s), zoning ordinances/maps, soil surveys, county land use and development plans, transportation plans (e.g., bikeways, park and ride, highway rest station plans), environmental impact statements, and numerous reports on county water/sewerage projects.
  - [Town of] Ballston, Excerpts from Exhibit E-Report, Burnt Hills-Ballston Lake Water District, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - [Town of] Ballston Lake, History and Origin, 2001 March (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - [Town of] Ballston Spa, Local Law Relating to Zoning of the Village of Ballston Spa, 1994 May (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - [Town of] Ballston Spa, Plan for Ballston- A Comprehensive Development Guide, 1964 November (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - [Town of] Ballston Spa, Planning Study, 1965 January (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - [Town of] Clifton Park, Bedrock Contours Maps, 1981 August (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - [Town of] Clifton Park, Capital Improvement Program, 1965 August (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - [Town of] Clifton Park, Clifton Park Master Plan Demographic Analysis, 1987 July (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - [Town of] Clifton Park, Community Facilities- Public Utilities, 1964 January (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - [Town of] Clifton Park, Crossroads and Canals: The History of Clifton Park…[Book], 1975 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - [Town of] Clifton Park, Crossroads and Canals: The History of Clifton Park [Book], 1985 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - [Town of] Clifton Park, Design and Construction Standards Testing and Inspection Procedures, 1988 January (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - [Town of] Clifton Park, Economic Base Study, 1963 August (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - [Town of] Clifton Park, Engineering Feasibility Report for the Town of Clifton Park Water Authority Water System (1 of 2), 1991 December (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - [Town of] Clifton Park, Engineering Feasibility Report for the Town of Clifton Park Water Authority Water System (2 of 2), 1991 December (Box 1, Folder 15)